http://www.ummera.com/privacy-policy

Home / Privacy Policy
Ummera is fully committed to preserving the privacy of all visitors to www.ummera.com Please read the following privacy policy to understand how we use and protect the information that you provide to us under the terms of the Irish Data Protection Acts 1988 and 2003 (“you”). By using the Ummera website you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy and, furthermore, by registering on this site, you consent to the collection, use and transfer of your information under the terms of this Privacy Policy.
1. Information that we collect from you
When you register with this site you will be asked to provide certain information about yourself including your name and contact details. We may also collect information about your usage of our website as well as information about you from information you post to the website or e-mails or letters you send to us either directly or indirectly by using our services.
We may transfer data that we collect from you to locations outside of the European Economic Area for processing and storing. Also, it may be processed by staff operating outside the European Economic Area who work for one of our suppliers e.g. staff engaged in the processing and concluding of your order and/or the processing of your payment details. By submitting your personal data you agree to this transfer, storing and processing. We shall take all reasonable steps to ensure that your data is treated securely and in agreement with this Privacy Policy.
2. Use of your information
We will use and analyse the information we collect so that we can administer, support, improve and develop our business. We may also use your information to contact you for your views on our services and to notify you occasionally about changes or developments to our services including (where you have consented) we might also use your information to let you know about other services which we offer which may be of interest to you and we may contact you by e-mail. If you change your mind about being contacted in the future, please let us know by contacting us on info@ummera.com and we shall immediately stop such contact.
3. Disclosure of your information
Subject to clause 1 above, we do not pass on your details to any third parties, however, if our business enters into a joint venture with or is sold to or merged with another business entity, your information may be disclosed to our new business partners or owners.
Our website contains links to other websites operated by third parties that we think may interest you. We will not share your information with these third parties and unless required to do so by law, we will not otherwise share, sell or distribute any of the information you provide to us without your consent. Such third parties are believed by us to have appropriate privacy standards and policies but we are not responsible for their actions or omissions, the content of their website or any products or services that they may offer.
4. Cookies
Cookies are small amounts of information which we store on your computer and our system will issue cookies to your computer when you log on to the site. Cookies make it easier for you to log on to and use the site during future visits. They also allow us to monitor website traffic and to personalise the content of the site for you. You may set up your computer to reject cookies although, in that case, you may not be able to use certain features on our site.
5. Security and data retention
We employ security measures to protect your information from access by unauthorised persons and against unlawful processing, accidental loss, destruction and damage. We will retain your information for a reasonable period or as long as the law requires.
6. Accessing and updating
You are entitled to see the information held about you and you may ask us to make any necessary changes to ensure that it is accurate and kept up to date. If you wish to do this, please contact us.
7. Changes to our privacy policy
Any changes to our privacy policy in the future will be posted to the site and, where appropriate, through e-mail notification.
8. Contact Us
All comments, queries and requests relating to our use of your information are welcomed and should be addressed to Ummera Smoked Products Limited, Flaxpond House, Inchybridge, Timoleague, Co. Cork, Ireland or, alternatively, sent by email to info@ummera.com
Search for:
Blog Archive Blog Archive
Select Month
November 2016
October 2016
September 2016
March 2016
May 2014
January 2014
For all enquiries please email info@ummera.com
Gift Vouchers Our delicious smoked products make for a very special gift indeed! Send a gift voucher to a friend or loved one today and they can redeem the voucher directly from our online shop!
Purchase gift voucher ›
Feedback We welcome all feedback from our customers.
If you would like to contact Ummera Smokehouse directly and tell us about your shopping experience, you can email us at info@ummera.com
We look forward to hearing from you!
Follow Ummera
Buy a gift voucher
Quality Irish gift ideas from Ummera Smokehouse.
